The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Twenty-Seventh Episode
Magic Water
I was deceived
by the fake Tink...
...and I was thrown down
into the valley.
There, a mysterious gas
blinded me...
...and I finally returned
to the castle with difficulty,
only to find
a fake Sapphire there.
But I will not give up!
Whatever happens,
I will thwart this conspiracy
and Dad and Mom...
Who's there?
This sounds to me like
the laughter of Mephisto!
Yes! And today I will succeed
in stealing your heart!
It's useless! Don't you want to know
where your father and mother are?
What? You know where they are?
Now I understand...
You kidnapped my father and my mother!
Please, tell me where they are!
I will tell you, if in exchange
you give me your heart!
Stone crane,
fly to my house!
- Where am I?
- This is my house!
Tell me...
Where are my father and my mother?
Fine, as promised I'll tell you:
they are on Snake Island.
- Snake Island?
- Yes! They are there, motionless...
...and they don't say a word!
- What do you mean?
With a spell of mine, I turned
them into stone statues...
and now they can't even move a hair.
Mom and Dad are stone statues?!
Untie this rope, I want
to go to Snake Island!
- Untie this rope!
- All right!
I'll untie you, but only after
you've given your heart to Hecate.
Hecate! Hecate, come here!
Hecate!
Hecate, answer me!
Hecate, wait for me!
Hecate, come out! Maybe
you don't like his heart?
Father... Mother...
I'm sorry!
I wish I could do it,
but I can't help you!
If only I could see..
But it's too late!
Soon Mephisto will return!
- Hecate, where are you?
- I'm here!
Hecate, come on, answer me!
Where are you, Hecate?
May I know where you've hidden yourself?
Answer me!
I've got it! She must have hidden
in one of these jars!
I saw you!
So you're in here!
I've caught you, Hecate!
Come out, Hecate!
Please, obey your father.
I'm sorry Dad..
Hecate, open the lid!
I won't scold you,
but please, come out!
I know you're hidden
in this jar!
Thank you, Hecate,
I am grateful to you for saving me
Hurry and get ready to run away!
Run, now!
If Dad finds out that the lid
doesn't open, he'll come back!
Please, Hecate!
Please, come out!
I can't break the jar with a
magic spell if you are inside!
Come on, Sapphire, hold
on until we get to a ship!
I would like to treat
your eyes, but I can't.
I'm already grateful to you
for bringing me this far, Hecate.
There's the ship!
Come on, be brave!
We have to reach Snake
Island before Dad arrives!
I'm afraid that Dad
is really angry!
I wonder how long
I've been asleep.
I thought the direction
had changed...
...while I was sleeping,
but it's the same!
- Are we at Snake Island already?
- Not yet!
I want to see my father and my mother
as soon as possible.
You will see them soon, Sapphire!
- That is the Island of Snakes!
- Really?! Finally, we are here!
Hold on tight to the boat,
there are many whirlpools.
We must be careful,
because they are very dangerous.
Hecate! Where are you, Hecate?
- I am safe, Sapphire!
Is everything okay? - Yes!
Even though it was tough, finally
we are on the Island of Snakes!
What?! This is it?
And where are they?
They must be somewhere
on this island!
Sapphire, quick, hide!
- What is happening?
- Be quiet! There are many...
...sea snakes on this island!
If they discover us, we will die!
Sapphire! It's on your head!
Let's get out of here!
Up!
We have almost arrived.
Sapphire, look!
There are your father and your mother!
Where are they, Hecate?
This is your mother, Sapphire.
This is her?!
This cold stone is my mother?
Oh, mother!
My mother!
Please, tell me: how
do I break the spell?
One way is to have
my father do it.
I really don't think he
would be willing to do it!
And another way is
to pour over them...
...the greatest possible amount of
the blood of the one who loves them.
The greatest possible
amount of blood?
I love them more than
anyone else! Then, if I pour...
...all my blood over them,
the spell will be broken!
- That's right, isn't it?
- But it's impossible!
It is possible! I can do it!
Father! Mother! I will break the
spell that Mephisto has cast on you!
No, Sapphire! If you do
such a thing, you will die!
- Let me go!
- Sapphire...!
- Hecate! Hecate!
- Here is my father!
- Mephisto...
- Sapphire, it's dangerous!
Sapphire!
- Sapphire!
- Father! Mother..
Throw that body overboard
and let the fish eat it!
But he is still alive!
He must have escaped
from some island.
To avoid unpleasant situations, it will
be better to throw him back into the sea.
It's a shame to throw him back
into the sea after we've saved him!
- Wait! Don't throw him overboard!
- At your orders, Captain!
Silver, don't you dare do
anything without my permission!
I want to take a look at
him. Bring him to my room!
I've hoped so much to be able to
see you again one day, Sapphire.
And that day has come!
But now sleep well...
...and try to recover your
health soon!
- Where am I?
- You've woken up!
Who's there? Who are you?
- It's me, Captain Blood!
- Captain Blood?!
Don't you remember me?
You saved me that time...
...when I was arrested
by the Grand Duke, a year ago!
And now, as you see,
I'm a pirate!
But what happened to your eyes?
Can't you see me?
What the hell happened to you?
Tell me, if you want.
It must have been a plot
by the Ice Queen.
- Ice Queen?!
- Exactly!
They say that soon
the Ice Queen's army
...will prepare
to occupy Silverland, understand?
Then Mephisto and the fake Sapphire...
Yes, they must be accomplices
of the Ice Queen.
It's just
the way she operates.
Damned Ice Queen!
As soon as I see her again, I'll kill her!
If you want to do that, for a start,
we have to heal your eyes!
Heal my eyes?
But can they be healed?
Pirates travel the world
and hear many things.
I have heard talk
of the Magic Spring!
- Magic Spring?!
- Yes!
If you wash your eyes
with its magic water,
the water will remove the poison
and soon you will be able to see again.
Really? Are you serious?
Do you think I will be able to see again?
We might encounter dangers
on the way to the Black Island,
where the Spring is located,
but do not fear, I will protect you!
How stupid Blood is!
I can't stand being entangled
...in a dangerous undertaking
because of that brat! Let's go!
It's cold on the deck,
let's go back to the cabin.
Damn Blood!
You will pay for this!
Why do you say that we
will encounter dangers?
Because to get there we
have to pass Wild Rock...
...and Koto Inlet.
- Are they very dangerous?
Don't worry! In the meantime
drink this, it'll warm you up.
No, I can't drink alcohol.
Then I'll give you something
that is much better than alcohol.
I think I put it here.
It's true that I helped you,
but why are you so kind to me?
Well, I can't answer you
just like that!
Here it is, I found it!
You'll see that this
will do you much more good than alcohol!
- But what is it?
- It's a dress.
I kept it because I was convinced
that I would meet you one day.
- Try it on! - Don't make
fun of me! I'm a boy!
Sapphire, even if you pretend to be
a boy, I know you're a girl.
Don't insist!
All right! All right, Sapphire!
For now I won't insist,
but please try it on if you have
some free time one day.
What's happening?
There's a rock in front of us!
- There's another one!
- Another one!
- Help!
Water will get in,
hurry up and repair it!
- The water has stopped!
- It's stopped!
Help, Blood!
The Wild Rock!
The Wild Rock...
Watch out!
- Is everything okay, Sapphire?
- Yes! But what the hell happened?
- The Wild Rock!
- The Wild Rock?!
But we're going to the Black Island,
where the magic Spring is!
Yes! I'll help you, Sapphire,
even if you don't want me to!
Hey, don't waste time!
Don't let the water in!
Sapphire, be careful!
Correct the course!
Damn it!
- Hurrah!
Silver, what have you done?
Listen, Captain, it seems
to me that you can't...
...see anything else
besides Sapphire!
- What?!
- Be more careful from now on!
The island! The island!
Sapphire, get up, the island is in sight!
I feel dazed!
There's a mermaid!
- I'm going!
- Me too!
Stay in your places!
Don't be fooled!
That song is a spell!
Oh, no, I feel dizzy too!
Sapphire...
Sapphire, thank you!
I've finally recovered.
If you want the sharks to eat you, go!
I will only stop at the Black Island!
Damn it! I can't stand working for a girl!
You'll pay for this too!
Sapphire, this is the Black Island, where the magic Spring is.
Silver, what do you need that saber for?
You never know who you might run into.
Blood, I hear the sound of water. Over there!
There it is!
It must be the magic spring.
Be careful, because the bottom is treacherous.
Wash them with care.
I can't see anything!
It's darker than ever!
Wash them! Wash them! Fill your eyes with water and wash them thoroughly!
- Well, Sapphire?
- Blood, watch out!
What are you doing, Silver?
Have you decided to betray me?
I've waited so long
for this moment!
Before someone stops
me, Blood... On guard!
Now I can see!
I can see!
Fine, you damned traitor!
Come on, show some guts!
Stop! Don't fight among yourselves!
Oh! Damn it!
Take this!
Wait! I'm fighting too, now!
You brat! You'll be the
first to die! Prepare yourself!
Now you're alone.
What do you want to do?
No, no, no! I surrender.
I don't want to fight anymore! Goodbye!
Are you okay, Blood? Wait,
I want to wash your wound
I'm perfectly fine, it's just a
scratch. You're always so strong.
But I still prefer the Sapphire
dressed like yesterday to this one.
- Did you say something?
- No, no, I didn't say anything!
But you should rest now.
It's a truly wonderful thing
that you can see again, isn't it?
Yes, Blood! And I owe
all of this only to you!
So, Sapphire, please,
be careful. All right?
Yes! Goodbye, Blood!
Sapphire, take care of yourself!
Goodbye, Blood!
Goodbye to everyone!
- Goodbye! Goodbye, Sapphire!
- Bye, Sapphire!
You'll see, now! I will
succeed in defeating...
...Queen Icicle and
protecting Silverland!
Father... Mother...
Please, wait for me!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP